好吧，来看看我们是怎么做的
All right, let's see how we did.
如果你勾选了 记录ID，天气条件ID，最低温
If you checked record ID, weather
condition ID, minimum temperature,
风速，湿度，最高温
wind speed, humidity,
maximum temperature,
日期，风向还有气压，你便选对了正确的答案
date, weather direction and
pressure, you've got this right.
从技术层面上说，我们可以包含日期或者时间
Now technically,
one could have included either date or
就像时间其实包含着日期
time, as time includes date.
月份在这里没有多大的必要
Month doesn't really
make any sense here.
但由于我们实际只显示日期，对于数据库来说，
But since we're really displaying the
date, it makes sense for the database to
最有意义地还是尽可能多地复制那些用来显示的项
actually replicate what's on
the display as much as possible.
单位应该存储在一个独立的首选项里
Units should be stored in
a separate table with preferences.
我们没有任何理由去存储我们不想显示的东西，比如说
There's no reason to store things
we aren't displaying, such as,
你懂的，降雨量或者平均温度
you know, rainfall or
average temperature.
除此之外，我们并不能从Openweather API中获取到这些
And besides, we cannot get these
from the OpenWeatherMap API.
我们确实需要 weather condition ID，因为我们需要用它去
We do need weather condition ID,
since we use this to
显示天气预报，并确定需要显示的画面
both display the forecast, and
determine the image to display.
最后，尽管ID在我们的UI界面中不显示
And finally,
while it's not displayed in our UI,
我们还是需要一个ID列用来唯一地标识每一行
we need an ID column to
uniquely identify each row.
正如我们讨论的
As discussed, it's required for
所有的SQLite 数据库表需要显示在Android list views视图中
all SQLI database tables that are going
to be displayed in Android list views.